<source>
<publisher/>
<publisherurl/>
<lastBuildDate/>
<job>
<title>
<![CDATA[ Delivery shreyansh - Hiring Immediately shreyansh ]]>
</title>
<date>
<![CDATA[ 2023-07-06 ]]>
</date>
<referencenumber>
<![CDATA[ 14937_ed454d4shreyanshnew234c114616a8cd07 ]]>
</referencenumber>
<url>
<![CDATA[ https://click.appcast.io/track/h346t57?cs=o8z&jg=6l6k&bid=rZ1shreyanshffa== ]]>
</url>
<company>
<![CDATA[ Delivery Driver INCC. ]]>
</company>
<sourcename/>
<city>
<![CDATA[ Marshall ]]>
</city>
<country>
<![CDATA[ United States ]]>
</country>
<state>
<![CDATA[ MO ]]>
</state>
<radius/>
<postalcode>
<![CDATA[ 65340 ]]>
</postalcode>
<streetaddress/>
<email/>
<description>
<![CDATA[ no boss? With the Spark Driver™ app, you can shop and deliver for customers of Walmart and other local businesses. Available in more than 3,650 cities and all 50 states, the Spark Driver platform makes it possible for you to reach thousands of customers! How it works Enroll using this link Download the Spark Driver app Choose from available offers you want to accept Features Have the freedom and flexibility to earn whenever it's convenient for you. Drivers keep 100% of tips earned Refer & Earn with our Referral Incentive Program. Refer a new driver from an eligible zone and you’ll earn an incentive when they enter your referral code. Incentive programs with a variety of offerings to help make it easier for all drivers to maximize their earning potential Free Walmart+ membership for qualified drivers. See Spark Driver Rewards Program at https://drive4spark.walmart.com/Spark%20Driver%20Rewards%20Program Requirements The Spark Driver app is available on both iOS and Android mobile devices. For best use, we recommend using iOS 11 and newer or Android 5.0 and higher. Additionally, all devices should have a camera with GPS Location Services. Prepaid devices do not support the Spark Driver app You must be 18 years of age or older to complete deliveries with the Spark Driver platform. A clean, smoke-free vehicle Valid proof of auto insurance Valid driver's license and clean driving record Authorization to work in the United States Consent to a background check Sign up now to start earning! ]]>
</description>
<salary/>
<education/>
<major_category/>
<minor_category/>
<requirements/>
<experience/>
<expirationdate/>
<remotetype/>
<workschedule/>
<jobtype/>
<cpc>
<![CDATA[ 0.26 ]]>
</cpc>
<mobile_friendly_apply>
<![CDATA[ No ]]>
</mobile_friendly_apply>
<html_jobs>
<![CDATA[ Yes ]]>
</html_jobs>
</job>
</source>
